so what are your plans
are you going on a trip yes
I'll be in Chicago my sister just gave birth to a child
I'll be assisting her for a few weeks
great send my congratulations to your sister
thanks is it a boy or a girl
a girl rose is her given name
what a lovely name yeah
this is named after our grandma
my kid is named after my grandmother as well
Marie is her given name that is also a lovely name
thank you is this your younger sister's first child
yes she is my first niece as well
she is also the family's first grandchild
what a unique gift yeah
my mom is overjoyed
she bought a lot of clothes for my niece already
that's fantastic
sorry I gotta go
I need to go to the airport by one PM okay
see you later